A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.2, Series 100 International - Series 253 Washington FA387a
Rockefeller Archive Center
- United States, 1929-1977; 200; 113 box(es)
  - United States - Social Sciences, 1950-1974; 200.S; 53 Cubic Feet; 133 __Boxes __53 cubic feet
    - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy - International Court Conference - Reports and Reprints, 1961-1963; 7 items contained in flders 4338-4339. (Box 508, Folder 4339)
    - Florida State University - Community Problems - (Desegregation) - Charles M. Grigg, Lewis M. Killian), 1960-1965 (Box 508, Folder 4340)
    - Florida State University - Community Problems - (Desegregation) - Charles M. Grigg, Lewis M. Killian), 1960-1965 (Box 508, Folder 4341)
    - Fordham University - Baerwald, Friedrich - (German Industrial Productivity), 1952 (Box 508, Folder 4342)
    - Fordham University - Remee, Peter P. - (International Law), 1954-1961 (Box 508, Folder 4343)
    - Foreign Affairs - (African Subscriptions), 1960-1961 (Box 508, Folder 4344)
    - Foreign Policy Association - Internship Program, 1950-1952, 1955 (Box 508, Folder 4345)
    - Foreign Policy Association - Internship Program, 1956-1963 (Box 509, Folder 4346)
    - Foreign Policy Association - Internship Program, 1956-1963 (Box 509, Folder 4347)
    - Foreign Policy Association - Internship Program, 1956-1963 (Box 509, Folder 4348)
    - Foreign Policy Association - Population Publication - ("The World Population Crisis"), 1968-1969 (Box 509, Folder 4349)
    - Foreign Policy Association - Wriston, Henry M. - (Foreign Service Recruitment), 1955 (Box 509, Folder 4350)
    - George Washington University - Dixon, Robert G. - (Legislative Apportionment), 1963-1965, 1968 (Box 509, Folder 4351)
    - George Washington University - Rommen, Heinrich A. - (Counter-Reformation Political Thought), 1954, 1959-1963 (Box 509, Folder 4352)
    - Goucher College - Neumann, William L. - (Nationalism Studies), 1961-1962, 1964 (Box 509, Folder 4353)
    - Halse, Michael C. - (Grant in Aid, Agriculture), 1961 (Box 509, Folder 4354)
    - Harvard University - Attitude Studies - (Louis Guttman, Samuel A. Stouffer), 1953-1955, 1958 (Box 509, Folder 4355)
    - Harvard University - Bailyn, Bernard - (Eighteenth Century Political Theory in the U.S.), 1963-1965 (Box 510, Folder 4356)
    - Harvard University - Beer, Samuel H. - (British Politics), 1956-1959, 1965 (Box 510, Folder 4357)
    - Harvard University - Berman, Harold J. - (U.S.S.R. Foreign Trade), 1955-1958 (Box 510, Folder 4358)
    - Harvard University - Child Development Study - (Sears, Robert R.), 1950-1956 (Box 510, Folder 4359)
    - Harvard University - Child Development Study - (Sears, Robert R.), 1950-1956 (Box 510, Folder 4360)
    - Harvard University - Child Development Study - (Sears, Robert R.), 1950-1956 (Box 510, Folder 4361)
    - Harvard University - Chinese Law - (Seminar), 1962-1965 (Box 510, Folder 4362)
    - Harvard University - Community Leadership - (Stouffer, Samuel A.), 1957-1961 (Box 510, Folder 4363)
    - Harvard University - Comparative Cultures - (Laboratory of Social Relations), 1948-1952 (Box 510, Folder 4364)
    - Harvard University - Comparative Cultures - (Laboratory of Social Relations), 1948-1952 (Box 510, Folder 4365)
    - Harvard University - Comparative Cultures - (Laboratory of Social Relations), 1953-1959, 1966 (Box 511, Folder 4366)
    - Harvard University - Constitutionalism - (Law School Convocation), 1954-1956 (Box 511, Folder 4367)
    - Harvard University - Disarmament Studies - (Joint Program With M.I.T.), 1960-1965 (Box 511, Folder 4368)
    - Harvard University - Disarmament Studies - (Joint Program With M.I.T.), 1960-1965 (Box 511, Folder 4368)
    - Harvard University - Report, "Strategy and Arms Control" - (Thomas C. Schelling, Morton H. Halperin), 1961 (Box 511, Folder 4369)
    - Harvard University - Report, "Strategy and Arms Control" - (Thomas C. Schelling, Morton H. Halperin), 1961 (Box 511, Folder 4370)
    - Harvard University - Draper, Theodore - (History of U.S. Communist Party), 1959-1964 (Box 511, Folder 4371)
    - Harvard University - Economic Research - (Leontief, Wassily W.), 1947-1958 (Box 512, Folder 4372)
    - Harvard University - Economic Research - (Leontief, Wassily W.), 1947-1958 (Box 512, Folder 4373)
    - Harvard University - Economic Research - (Leontief, Wassily W.), 1947-1958 (Box 512, Folder 4374)
    - Harvard University - Economic Research - (Leontief, Wassily W.), 1947-1958 (Box 512, Folder 4375)
    - Harvard University - Economic Research - (Leontief, Wassily W.), 1947-1958 (Box 512, Folder 4376)
    - Harvard University - Economic Research - (Leontief, Wassily W.), 1947-1958 (Box 512, Folder 4377)
    - Harvard University - Economic Research - (Leontief, Wassily W.), 1959-1970, 1972 (Box 513, Folder 4378)
    - Harvard University - Economic Research - (Leontief, Wassily W.), 1959-1970, 1972 (Box 513, Folder 4379)
    - Harvard University - Economic Research - Reports and Reprints, 1954-1956, 1963, 1970; 7 items (Box 513, Folder 4380)
    - Harvard University - Emerson, Rupert - (Travel Grant, Political Science), 1966-1968 (Box 513, Folder 4381)
    - Harvard University - Entrepeneurial History - (Cole, Arthur E.), 1947-1951 (Box 513, Folder 4382)
    - Harvard University - Entrepeneurial History - (Cole, Arthur E.), 1947-1951 (Box 513, Folder 4383)
    - Harvard University - Entrepeneurial History - (Cole, Arthur E.), 1947-1951 (Box 513, Folder 4384)
    - Harvard University - Entrepeneurial History - (Cole, Arthur E.), 1952-1959 (Box 514, Folder 4385)
    - Harvard University - Entrepeneurial History - (Cole, Arthur E.), 1952-1959 (Box 514, Folder 4386)
    - Harvard University - Entrepeneurial History - Atherton, Lewis E., 1953-1954 (Box 514, Folder 4387)
    - Harvard University - Evans, John W. - (Tariff and Trade Negotiations), 1964-1966 (Box 514, Folder 4388)
    - Harvard University - Fuller, Lon L. - (Social Order), 1959-1961, 1963-1964 (Box 514, Folder 4389)
    - Harvard University - Halperin, Morton W. - (Chinese Military Power), 1961-1965 (Box 514, Folder 4390)
    - Harvard University - Hartz, Louis - (Westernization in the Third World), 1954, 1956-1959, 1969-1972 (Box 514, Folder 4391)
    - Harvard University - Hoffman, Stanley - (French Politics, 1933-1944), 1968-1970 (Box 514, Folder 4392)
    - Harvard University - International Affairs - (Bowie, Robert R.), 1957-1967 (Box 515, Folder 4393)
    - Harvard University - International Affairs - (Bowie, Robert R.), 1957-1967 (Box 515, Folder 4394)
    - Harvard University - International Affairs - (Bowie, Robert R.), 1957-1967 (Box 515, Folder 4395)
    - Harvard University - International Affairs - (Bowie, Robert R.), 1957-1967 (Box 515, Folder 4396)
    - Harvard University - International Affairs - Kato, Tadao, 1959, 1961 (Box 515, Folder 4397)
    - Harvard University - International Affairs - Pirngadie, Rudi, 1959, 1961 (Box 515, Folder 4398)
    - Harvard University - International Affairs - Razzaq, Abdur, 1956-1959, 1961 (Box 515, Folder 4399)
    - Harvard University - International Affairs - Singh, Lallan Prasad, 1959, 1961 (Box 515, Folder 4400)
    - Harvard University - International Affairs - Visiting Scholars, 1958-1960 (Box 515, Folder 4401)
    - Harvard University - International Affairs - Visiting Scholars, 1958-1960 (Box 515, Folder 4402)
    - Harvard University - International Affairs - Visiting Scholars - Papers, 1959; 5 items contained in folders 4403-4404. (Box 516, Folder 4403)
    - Harvard University - International Affairs - Visiting Scholars - Papers, 1959; 5 items contained in folders 4403-4404. (Box 516, Folder 4404)
    - Harvard University - International Affairs - Visiting Scholars - Papers (French Seminar), 1959 (Box 516, Folder 4405)
    - Harvard University - International Affairs - Visiting Scholars - Papers, 1964-1965; 8 items contained in folders 4406-4409. (Box 516, Folder 4406)
    - Harvard University - International Affairs - Visiting Scholars - Papers, 1964-1965; 8 items contained in folders 4406-4409. (Box 516, Folder 4407)
    - Harvard University - International Affairs - Visiting Scholars - Papers, 1964-1965; 8 items contained in folders 4406-4409. (Box 516, Folder 4408)
    - Harvard University - International Affairs - Visiting Scholars - Papers, 1964-1965; 8 items contained in folders 4406-4409. (Box 516, Folder 4409)
    - Harvard University - International Agribusiness Coordination Project - (Business School), 1970-1971 (Box 517, Folder 4410)
    - Harvard University - Input-Output Study - (Economic Research Project-Investments), 1961 (Box 517, Folder 4411)
    - Harvard University - Jackson, Barbara Ward - (Visiting Lecturer, International Relations), 1955-1956, 1958 (Box 517, Folder 4412)
    - Harvard University - Jurisprudence - (Law Reiew Studies), 1954-1956 (Box 517, Folder 4413)
    - Harvard University - Jurisprudence - Hart, Herbert L.A. - (Visiting Professor), 1954-1958 (Box 517, Folder 4414)
    - Harvard University - Kress Library Catalogue - (Economics and Business Titles), 1953-1955, 1958 (Box 517, Folder 4415)
    - Harvard University - Land Use Control Seminar - (Haar, Charles M.), 1959-1962 (Box 517, Folder 4416)
    - Harvard University - Land Use Control Seminar - Transcript, 1961 (Box 517, Folder 4417)
    - Harvard University - Land Use Control Seminar - Transcript, 1961 (Box 517, Folder 4418)
    - Harvard University - Law School - Choi, Woosang - (Grant in Aid), 1956-1957, 1959-1962 (Box 517, Folder 4419)
    - Harvard University - Law School - Ethical Problems - (Lon L. Fuller, David F. Carvers), 1951-1953 (Box 517, Folder 4420)
    - Harvard University - Law School - Ethical Problems - (Lon L. Fuller, David F. Carvers), 1954-1957, 1962 (Box 518, Folder 4421)
    - Harvard University - Law School - Haar, Charles M. - (English Land Use Planning), 1954-1962 (Box 518, Folder 4422)
    - Harvard University - Law School - Joe, Kyi Dai - (Grant in Aid), 1955-1957, 1959 (Box 518, Folder 4423)
    - Harvard University - Law School - Lindbeck, John M. H. - (Chinese Communist Political Process), 1961-1963 (Box 518, Folder 4424)
    - Harvard University - McCloskey, Robert G. - (U.S. Supreme Court and Civil Liberties), 1953-1956 (Box 518, Folder 4425)
    - Harvard University - Mansfield, Harvey C. - (Origins of Representative Government), 1964-1967 (Box 518, Folder 4426)
    - Harvard University - Market Economy Conference - (Villa Serbelloni), 1965 (Box 518, Folder 4427)
    - Harvard University - Mihaly, Zoltan M. - (Grant in Aid, Hungarian Refugee), 1959-1960 (Box 518, Folder 4428)
    - Harvard University - Oliver, Douglas L. - (French Oceania Field Study, Anthropology), 1953-1956 (Box 518, Folder 4429)
    - Harvard University - Parel, Anthony J. - (Indian Democracy), 1959-1962 (Box 519, Folder 4430)
    - Harvard University - Political Behavior - (State Election Statistics) - (Key, V.O.), 1950-1959 (Box 519, Folder 4431)
    - Harvard University - Political Behavior - (State Election Statistics) - (Key, V.O.), 1950-1959 (Box 519, Folder 4432)
    - Harvard University - Political Ideology - (Seminr), 1956-1958, 1960 (Box 519, Folder 4433)
    - Harvard University - Political Theory (and Institutions), 1956, 1958-1962 (Box 519, Folder 4434)
    - Harvard University - Profits Study - (Lintner, John V. et al.), 1950-1959, 1961-1964 (Box 519, Folder 4435)
    - Harvard University - Profits Study - (Lintner, John V. et al.), 1950-1959, 1961-1964 (Box 519, Folder 4436)
    - Harvard University - Profits Study - (Lintner, John V. et al.), 1950-1959, 1961-1964 (Box 519, Folder 4437)
    - Harvard University - Research Training - (Laboratory of Social Relations), 1955-1958 (Box 520, Folder 4438)
    - Harvard University - Role Conflicts - (Gross, Neal), 1952-1958 (Box 520, Folder 4439)
    - Harvard University - Role Conflicts - Report, 1956 (Box 520, Folder 4440)
    - Harvard University - Russian Studies, 1960-1964 (Box 520, Folder 4441)
    - Harvard University - Russian Studies - Faculty, 1953-1956, 1958 (Box 520, Folder 4442)
    - Harvard University - Russian Studies - Volin, 1956, 1959, 1965 (Box 520, Folder 4443)
    - Harvard University - Russian Studies - (A-Z), 1959-1961 (Box 520, Folder 4444)
    - Harvard University - Science and Public Policy - (Graduate School of Public Administration), 1957-1965, 1968 (Box 520, Folder 4445)
    - Harvard University - Science and Public Policy - (Graduate School of Public Administration), 1957-1965, 1968 (Box 520, Folder 4446)
    - Harvard University - Science and Public Policy - (Graduate School of Public Administration), 1957-1965, 1968 (Box 520, Folder 4447)
    - Harvard University - Science and Public Policy - (Graduate School of Public Administration), 1957-1965, 1968 (Box 520, Folder 4448)
    - Harvard University - Small Groups Study - (Robert F. Bales, Neal Gross), 1949-1957 (Box 521, Folder 4449)
    - Harvard University - Small Groups Study - (Robert F. Bales, Neal Gross), 1949-1957 (Box 521, Folder 4450)
    - Harvard University - Ulam, Adam B. - (Modern Socialist Movements), 1955-1958, 1960 (Box 521, Folder 4451)
    - Harvard University - Urban Expenditure - (Voting Behavior) - (Edward C. Banfield, James Q. Wilson), 1961-1966 (Box 521, Folder 4452)
    - Haverford College - Freund, Gerald - (West German Foreign Policy), 1959-1960 (Box 521, Folder 4453)
    - Haverford College - Technical Assistance (to Underdeveloped Countries) - (Case Studies), 1951-1956 (Box 521, Folder 4454)
    - Haverford College - Technical Assistance (to Underdeveloped Countries) - (Case Studies), 1951-1956 (Box 521, Folder 4455)
    - Haverford College - Technical Assistance - Capers, circa 1953; 4 items (Box 521, Folder 4456)
    - Hobart College - Smith, Maynard O. - (Natural Law and the U.S. Constitution), 1956-1957 (Box 521, Folder 4457)
    - Howard University - Fall, Bernard B. - (Indochinese Foreign Policies), 1961-1964 (Box 522, Folder 4458)
    - Howard University - Tate, Merze - (Australian Expansion), 1960-1962, 1965, 1967 (Box 522, Folder 4459)
    - Humbolt State College - Gimbel, John - (U.S.-German Relations after 1945), 1960-1966 (Box 522, Folder 4460)
    - Humbolt State College - Gimbel, John - Reprints, 1959-1960, 1963, 1965; 5 items (Box 522, Folder 4461)
    - Hunter College - Richter, Melvin - (French Political Sociology), 1959-1963 (Box 522, Folder 4462)
    - Hunter College - Union-Management Relations (U.S. and Germany) - (Hoeniger, Heinrich), 1952-1959 (Box 522, Folder 4463)
    - Hunter College - Union-Management Relations (U.S. and Germany) - (Hoeniger, Heinrich), 1952-1959 (Box 522, Folder 4464)
    - Indiana University - Hall, Jerome - (Western European Legal Theory), 1960-1962, 1964 (Box 522, Folder 4465)
    - Indiana University - Jelavich, Barbara - (Greek-Russian Relations), 1962-1964, 1966 (Box 522, Folder 4466)
    - Indiana University - Muller, Herbert J. - (Political Freedom, Cross-Cultural Study), 1959-1961 (Box 522, Folder 4467)
    - Indiana University - Schweitzer, Arthur - (Nazi Economy, 1937-1942), 1965-1966 (Box 522, Folder 4468)
    - Indiana University - Vatikiotis, P. J. - (Arab Politics), 1958-1963 (Box 523, Folder 4469)
    - Indiana University - Vatikiotis, P. J. - (Arab Politics), 1958-1963 (Box 523, Folder 4470)
    - Indiana University - Wandycz, Piotr Stefan - (U.S.S.R.-Poland Relations, 1917-1921), 1964-1966 (Box 523, Folder 4471)
    - Institute for Advanced Study - Earle, Edward M. - (Travel Grant), 1948-1949 (Box 523, Folder 4472)
    - Institute for Advanced Study - Freund, Gerald - (Soviet-German Relations), 1954-1957 (Box 523, Folder 4473)
    - Institute for Advanced Study - International Air Law - (Cooper, John C.), 1945-1952, 1956 (Box 523, Folder 4474)
    - Institute for Advanced Study - International Air Law - (Cooper, John C.), 1945-1952, 1956 (Box 523, Folder 4475)
    - Institute for Advanced Study - International Air Law - Reprints, 1945-1947 (Box 523, Folder 4476)
    - Institute for Advanced Study - Intervention in Russia (1918) - (Seminar), 1956-1957 (Box 523, Folder 4477)
    - Institute for Advanced Study - Kennan, George F. - (U.S. Foreign Policy), 1950-1956 (Box 523, Folder 4478)
    - Institute for Advanced Study - Lindberg, John - (Publication Costs of Foundations of Social Survival), 1945-1950, 1957-1966 (Box 523, Folder 4479)
    - Institute for Advanced Study - Niebuhr, Reinhold - (Moral Implications of International Relations), 1956-1960 (Box 524, Folder 4480)
    - Institute for Advanced Study - Social Sciences - (General Support), 1957-1958, 1962, 1964 (Box 524, Folder 4481)
    - Inter-University Committee on Travel Grants - Exchange Program - (Grant in Aid, Indiana University), 1952-1963 (Box 524, Folder 4482)
    - Iowa Child Welfare Research Station - (Child Development Study) - (Sears, Robert R.), 1946-1950, 1953 (Box 524, Folder 4483)
    - Iowa State College - Agricultural Economics (in India) - (Heady, Earl O.), 1958-1962 (Box 524, Folder 4484)
    - Iowa State College - Agricultural Economics (in India) - (Heady, Earl O.), 1958-1962 (Box 524, Folder 4485)
    - Iowa State College - Kozlik, Adolf - (Refugee Scholars, Economics), 1938-1941, 1943 (Box 524, Folder 4486)
    - Japan Society Inc. - Cohen, Jerome B. - (Japan's Economic Recovery), 1952, 1956-1958 (Box 524, Folder 4487)
    - Jefferies, Leonard Jr. - (Politics and Development in the Ivory Coast), 1965-1966 (Box 524, Folder 4488)
    - Johns, David H. - (Travel Grant, Political Science), 1962-1964 (Box 525, Folder 4489)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Gatzke, Hans W. - (German Foreign Policy, 1919-1933), 1955-1958, 1961-1964 (Box 525, Folder 4490)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Lichtblau, George E. - (Labour Movement in the British Commonwealth), 1963-1966 (Box 525, Folder 4491)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Lichtblau, George E. - Typescript, circa 1965 (Box 525, Folder 4492)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Lichtblau, George E. - Typescript, circa 1965 (Box 525, Folder 4493)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Lichtblau, George E. - Typescript, circa 1965 (Box 525, Folder 4494)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Political Economy - (Visiting Professorships), 1951-1961, 1963 (Box 525, Folder 4495)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Political Economy - (Visiting Professorships), 1951-1961, 1963 (Box 525, Folder 4496)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Political Economy - Research Guidance Program, 1953-1957, 1959 (Box 525, Folder 4497)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Rourke, Francis E. - (U.S. Urbanism and Democratic Development), 1957-1964 (Box 526, Folder 4498)
    - Johns Hopkins University - School of Advanced International Studies, 1940, 1959-1961, 1963-1966, 1970 (Box 526, Folder 4499)
    - Johns Hopkins University - School of Advanced International Studies, 1940, 1959-1961, 1963-1966, 1970 (Box 526, Folder 4500)
    - Johns Hopkins University - School of Advanced International Studies - Blanchet, Jeremy - (West German Strategic Policy), 1961-1964 (Box 526, Folder 4501)
    - Johns Hopkins University - School of Advanced International Studies - Foreign Policy, 1953-1954, 1956-1963 (Box 526, Folder 4502)
    - Johns Hopkins University - School of Advanced International Studies - Foreign Policy, 1953-1954, 1956-1963 (Box 526, Folder 4503)
    - Johns Hopkins University - School of Advanced International Studies - Foreign Policy, 1953-1954, 1956-1963 (Box 526, Folder 4504)
    - Johns Hopkins University - School of Advanced International Studies - Foreign Policy, 1964-1969, 1971 (Box 527, Folder 4505)
    - Johns Hopkins University - School of Advanced International Studies - Foreign Policy - Papers, 1958-1961; 5 items contained in folders 4506-4507. (Box 527, Folder 4506)
    - Johns Hopkins University - School of Advanced International Studies - Foreign Policy - Papers, 1958-1961; 5 items contained in folders 4506-4507. (Box 527, Folder 4507)
    - Johns Hopkins University - School of Advanced International Studies - Hammond, Paul Y. - (Militarism and Foreign Policy), 1958, 1960-1962, 1964 (Box 527, Folder 4508)
    - Johns Hopkins University - School of Advanced International Studies - Hilsman, Roger - (U.S. Congress and Foreign Policy), 1957-1959 (Box 527, Folder 4509)
    - Johns Hopkins University - School of Advanced International Studies - Khadduri, Majid - (Travel Grant, Middle East Political Trends), 1960-1965 (Box 527, Folder 4510)
    - Johns Hopkins University - School of Advanced International Studies - LeFever, Ernest W. - (Ethics and Foreign Policy), 1954-1959 (Box 527, Folder 4511)
    - Johns Hopkins University - School of Advanced International Studies - Lim Tay Boh - (Visiting Lecturer), 1955-1958 (Box 527, Folder 4512)
    - Johns Hopkins University - School of Advanced International Studies - Lineberger, Paul M. A. - (Kuomintang Study), 1953-1957 (Box 527, Folder 4513)
    - Johns Hopkins University - School of Advanced International Studies - Liska, George - (Eurafrican Regional Structures), 1961-1964 (Box 528, Folder 4514)
    - Johns Hopkins University - School of Advanced International Studies - Manigat, Leslie F. - (U.S. and French-Haitian Relations, 1888-1915), 1963-1964 (Box 528, Folder 4515)
    - Johns Hopkins University - School of Advanced International Studies - Purcell, Victor W.W.S. - (Visiting Professorship), 1955-1956 (Box 528, Folder 4516)
    - Johns Hopkins University - School of Advanced International Studies - Southeast Asia Conference, 1951-1956 (Box 528, Folder 4517)
    - Johns Hopkins University - School of Advanced International Studies - Southeast Asia Program, 1953-1960, 1962 (Box 528, Folder 4518)
    - Johns Hopkins University - School of Advanced International Studies - Southeast Asia Program, 1953-1960, 1962 (Box 528, Folder 4519)
    - Johns Hopkins University - School of Advanced International Studies - Southeast Asia Program, 1953-1960, 1962 (Box 528, Folder 4520)
    - Johns Hopkins University - School of Advanced International Studies - Tarr, David W. - (U.S. Overseas Military Bases and Strategy), 1961-1965 (Box 528, Folder 4521)
    - Johns Hopkins University - School of Advanced International Studies - Taylor, Philip B., Jr. - (Uruguayan Politics), 1964-1965 (Box 529, Folder 4522)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Smith, David G. - (Development of Marxism), 1953-1956 (Box 529, Folder 4523)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Trade Unionism - (Leiserson, William M.), 1944-1959 (Box 529, Folder 4524)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Trade Unionism - (Leiserson, William M.), 1944-1959 (Box 529, Folder 4525)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Tucker, Robert W. - (Nuclear Age Policies), 1953-1954, 1956-1960, 1964 (Box 529, Folder 4526)
    - Joint Committee for the Effective Administration of Justice - (American Bar Association, Tom C. Clark), 1961-1962, 1966 (Box 529, Folder 4527)
    - Kenyon College - English, Raymond - (Anglo-American Constitutional Development), 1955-1959 (Box 529, Folder 4528)
    - Lawrence College - Riker, William H. - (Theory of Federalism), 1954-1958, 1966 (Box 529, Folder 4529)
    - League of Women Voters - Overseas Education Fund - (Latin American Women), 1961-1968 (Box 530, Folder 4530)
    - League of Women Voters - Overseas Education Fund - (Latin American Women), 1961-1968 (Box 530, Folder 4531)
    - League of Women Voters - Overseas Education Fund - (Latin American Women), 1961-1968 (Box 530, Folder 4532)
    - League of Women Voters - Overseas Education Fund - (Latin American Women), 1961-1968 (Box 530, Folder 4533)
    - League of Women Voters - Overseas Education Fund - (Latin American Women), 1961-1968 (Box 530, Folder 4534)
    - Lebanon Valley College - Richards, Benjamin A. - (U.S. Supreme Court and Civil Liberties, 1919-1961), 1961-1962, 1964 (Box 530, Folder 4535)